# **Brian Zauner**

binrz00@hotmail.com || 612-720-5686

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I have been a line cook for 13 years, and a commercial fisherman for 3 seasons. I am currently enrolled in a coding boot camp. I bring a strong work ethic to every job I take, and I always leave a company better than when I first arrived. I have always worked long hours without getting tired. I can identify an issue before it becomes a problem. I can work well with all different personalities. I also usually improve efficiency in any working environment.

# SKILLS

I have experience in HTML, CSS, Javascript, Node.js, and Jquery. I have also used a variety of API's and have a working knowledge of local storage, flexbox, and DOM manipulation.

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Crew Member**

John Perkins Enterprises – Sweet, Idaho | August 2019 – September 2019

- Provided reports and other information to managers and Alaska Fish and Game
- Monitored tanks and controlled filling
- Prepared for docking and departures
- Light crane operations
- Navigation and maneuvering from Dutch Harbor, Alaska through Canada, and down to Seattle, Washington
- Performed all duties requested by the captain

### **Crew Member**

Kirsten Marie Tendering – Seattle, Washington | May 2019 – August 2019

- Provided reports and other information to managers and Alaska Fish and Game
- Prepared for docking and departures
- Light crane operations
- Managed food, fish, and net accounts for all the gillnetters in the district
- Navigate and maneuver from the fishery to the plant

- Navigate and maneuver from Seattle, Washington through Canada, and up to Bristol Bay, Alaska
- Performed all duties requested by the captain

#### **Lead line cook**

The Grumpy Minnow Center City – Center City, MN | January 2019 – May 2019

- Collaborated with the head chef to discuss menu items and executions
- Prepared food orders following food safety protocols
- Managed cleaning and sanitation of the work area before leaving
- Assisted in the line configuration for optimized food service
- Prepared food before service for optimized food service

### **Line Cook**

Agua Forest Lake – Forest Lake, MN | September 2018 – January 2018

- Received orders, prepared, and delivered quality food
- Cleaned and sanitized work area and utensils
- Prepared food beforehand to expedite food service
- Stocked the kitchen when the food order arrived
- Followed all rules and regulations for safe food handling

# **EDUCATION**

# **Coding boot camp certificate**

University of Minnesota | Minneapolis, MN | Febuary 2020